In these 108 names, if you have noticed,
Se avete notato, questi centootto nomi hanno mostrato
And that is also – it is very much related to Prana, it gives you Prana.
E ciò è anche strettamente collegato al Prana, vi dà il Prana.
Prana is the vital breath that we take – breathe in and breathe out.
Il Prana è il soffio vitale che riceviamo quando inspiriamo ed espiriamo.
So it is related to the right side. Then also it is related to eternity, Anantaye.
Ciò è dunque connesso al lato destro, ed anche all’eternità, Anantaye.
Ananta is the snake - the Shesha - which is the brother of Vishnu.
Ananta è il serpente Shesha, il quale è fratello di Vishnu.
So it is He who is represented here as Kartikeya.
È lui quindi ad essere rappresentato qui come Kartikeya.
He is called as Ananta. So he is the fire.
È lui ad essere chiamato Ananta. Quindi, è il fuoco.
He is the one who ignites within you the capacity to consume the force,
È lui ad accendervi dentro la capacità di consumare, la forza,
also the capacity to command the people
così come la capacità di comandare gli altri,
and also the capacity to be a person full of brilliance.
ed anche di essere persone molto brillanti.
You see, an innocent person could be very brilliant.
Le persone innocenti possono essere molto brillanti.
All these capacities are expressed in Kartikeya’s Swarupa, in His state.
Tutte queste capacità sono espresse nella forma, nello stato di Kartikeya.
Today, by worshipping Kartikeya we have to know
Oggi, mentre adoriamo Kartikeya, dobbiamo renderci conto
that Kartikeya is now awakened within us.
che ora Kartikeya è risvegliato in noi.
And with that capacity we have to fight.
E con questa capacità dobbiamo combattere.
Ultimately, He is the Nishkalanka. He is the one who is the final.
Infine, lui è Nishkalanka. È colui che è l’ultima (incarnazione).
So from Ganesha to Christ to Nishkalanka:
Quindi si passa da Ganesha a Cristo a Nishkalanka:
these are the three stages into which the innocence has gone.
queste sono le tre fasi attraversate dall’innocenza.
From Ganesha to Kartikeya and now to Christ.
Da Ganesha a Kartikeya ed ora a Cristo.
And from Christ to Nishkalanka.
Poi, da Cristo a Nishkalanka.
In the form of Nishkalanka He is innocent,
Nella forma di Nishkalanka lui è innocente,
so there is no Kalanka, there is no spot on Him, nothing.
così che su di lui non vi è kalanka, nessuna macchia, niente.
He is absolutely clean, immaculate; plus, He is fiery.
È assolutamente puro, immacolato; inoltre, è ardente.
Plus, He has all the qualities of Ekadasha Rudra,
E possiede anche tutte le qualità di Ekadasha Rudra,
means the eleven qualities or the forces of Shiva, which can kill.
vale a dire gli undici attributi o poteri distruttivi di Shiva.
So He has a capacity to kill and destroy that is evil
È capace di annientare, di distruggere il male
and to give blessings and courage to His followers.
e di dare benedizioni e coraggio ai suoi devoti.
This is the last incarnation, which is called as Kalki.
Questa è l’ultima incarnazione, chiamata Kalki.
In normal words you call it Kalki,
Normalmente voi la chiamate Kalki,
is actually Nishkalanka, in the white horse.
ma in realtà è Nishkalanka, sul cavallo bianco.
So, it is the Kartikeya who sits on the white horse.
Quindi, è Kartikeya il cavaliere
So how innocence grows within you now is up to the point of Kartikeya.
Adesso l’innocenza dentro di voi raggiunge il livello di Kartikeya.
This has been today done on this land, Deutschland as you call it,
Questo è stato compiuto oggi in questo paese
where Kartikeya is to be born within you, is to be awakened in you.
nel quale Kartikeya deve nascere in voi, deve essere risvegliato in voi.
May God bless you.
Dio vi benedica.